Okay.
When you listen to that recording of Tory Lanez
apologizing to Kelsey,
there are some basic things that are gonna be said.
Something I hear a lot of people saying is,
you know, when I hear that recording,
it sounds like he's apologizing for something else.
When he is saying,
you know what I'm saying, when I got to that house.
That lets you know that the context of his conversation
is about what's happening that night.
Now when people are like, oh, well,
he could be apologizing for anything
that happened that night.
Okay.
He then also says,
I promise I know she probably never, ever
gonna talk to me ever again, but...
This is what I'm talking about with contact.
Him stating,
That is a thing that happened that night.
Well, you know, Kelsey is
because why would you answer the phone
of somebody who just shot your friend?
Now as somebody who has had a rapper extort them
for money by using a picture that was not taken
with my consent.
And then when they called me,
I still answered the phone.
I can understand because...
Yep.
If you want to hear what else I got to say,
you got to go to my Patreon,
theamandiverse.com.
I can't give it all the way here,
but I did do 10 minutes worth of it.
So it is very thorough.
So I'll see you there with me and the SEAL squad.
But you did it.
But I'm back.
You got to watch me!
You guys can start a game.
Alright!
Come on!
See you.
Peace!
Friends,
friends ofibel.
I was mad Brother Kanal!
No question!
I have a dog!
Come on!
According to my family,
me,
it has an expression.
Let me see that!
Sounds like this.
It...
You were a dog!
It's the dog.
For me!
There...
Because of it!
I used to have a dog.